welcome to another tutorial in this
欢迎使用本教程中的另一个教程
video we'll be learning about the rotate
我们将学习有关旋转的视频
tool and also the scale tool which will
工具和缩放工具 该工具将
let us scale and rotate our image or
让我们缩放和旋转我们的图像或
just a certain selected part of our
只是我们的某个精选部分
image as well so to get started I'm
图像也是如此 为了开始 我是
going to control Z will undo all these
转到Control Z将撤消所有这些操作
changes go ahead and locate these tools
继续进行更改并找到这些工具
if you hover over it tells you about
如果你将鼠标悬停在上面 它会告诉你
them the rotate tool shift R is a
其中 旋转工具Shift R是
shortcut to access it and the scale tool
访问它和缩放工具的快捷方式
is right next to it it's shift s again
就在它旁边 又是换班的S
your icons may look a little bit
你的图标可能看起来有点像
different than mine but don't worry
和我的不一样 但别担心
about that when we click on the tool we
关于这一点 当我们点击工具时 我们
get more options for it down below
在下面获得更多选项
sometimes for whatever reason you may be
有时 无论出于什么原因 你都会
on a different transform mode you might
在不同的转换模式下 您可以
be transforming your selection in this
正在改变您的选择
case you might get an error message or
如果您可能收到一条错误消息或
if you have something selected say we
如果您选择了什么 请说我们
were using the selection tool to select
我们使用选择工具来选择
a certain area we could rotate just the
某一特定区域我们可以只旋转
selection but you probably don't want to
选择 但您可能不想
do that right off if we do this and hit
如果我们这样做 然后打出
rotate it's just going to rotate our
旋转它只是要旋转我们的
selection and not our image so make sure
而不是我们的形象 所以要确保
on the mode you're on the transform
在你正在转型的模式上
layer not selection or path I'm going to
我要转到的层不是选区或路径
go to right click and just go to select
转到右键单击 然后只需转到选择
all so we're selecting our entire image
所以我们选择了我们的整个形象
and then with the rotation tool selected
然后选择旋转工具
and in the transform mode under layer we
在Layer WE下的变换模式中
can just left click and hold and move
只需左键单击并按住并移动
around like from right to left or up and
就像从右到左或从上到右
down to rotate this image when we think
向下旋转这张图像 当我们认为
we have it where we want we can click
我们把它放在我们想要的地方我们可以点击
rotate and it will rotate it to that
旋转 它会把它旋转到那个位置
position notice we've kind of cut off we
位置通知我们已经切断了我们的
haven't really cut off these areas
并没有真正切断这些区域
they're still there but they are outside
他们还在那里 但他们在外面
of our project or outside of the size of
在我们的项目中 还是在
our image so we would need to either
我们的形象 所以我们需要
resize our image to get those or scale
调整我们的图像大小以获得这些或缩放
down our selection so that brings us
减少我们的选择 这将为我们带来
into the next tool if we wanted to keep
如果我们想继续使用下一个工具
these areas and maybe put a color in
这些区域 也许会加入一种颜色
over top of this transparency we can
在这种透明度之上 我们可以
left-click and select the scale tool and
左键单击并选择缩放工具 然后
it behaves very similarly we can just
它的行为非常相似 我们可以
left click and hold and scale down and
左键单击并按住 然后按比例缩小
scale the size of our selected area
缩放我们所选区域的大小
which in this case was the whole image
在这种情况下 这就是整个图像
the scale tool also has this little box
缩放工具还有这个小方框
in the center if we left click and hold
在中间 如果我们左键点击并按住
that it also has a move function so we
它也有移动功能 所以我们
could move this and keep scaling it down
可以移动它并继续缩小规模
by just left clicking and holding
只需左键点击并按住
anywhere or we can also scale by
任何地方 或者我们也可以通过
dragging these little boxes on the
把这些小盒子拖到
corners we can even scale looks like
我们甚至可以伸缩的角落看起来像
it's gonna scale uniformly but there's
它将统一扩展 但有
some options we could change if we
一些我们可以改变的选择如果我们
wanted to squish this down we could come
想把这个压下来 我们可以来
over here under the options and check
在这里的选项下 勾选
this box here that says keep aspect
这个框上写着保持纵横比
ratio or rather uncheck it and if we do
或者更确切地说 取消选中它 如果我们这样做了
that then it'll allow us to squish this
这样我们就可以把它压扁了
down and kind of make it not not scale
向下 让它不会变得没有规模
it uniformly if that makes sense so pay
如果这样做有意义 它会统一支付
attention to the options we have over
注意我们已有的选择
here and that's gonna help you out a lot
这里 这会对你有很大的帮助
with these tools let's jump over to a
有了这些工具 让我们跳到
different one I'm hit control Z and undo
不同的是 我按下了Ctrl Z 然后撤消
everything we did to this let's go to an
我们对此所做的一切让我们去一个
image here actually let's do this one
这里的图像实际上让我们做这一张
real quick so in this image that has the
非常快 所以在这张图中有
horizon is sort of off it's not the
地平线有点不对劲 不是
level and if we wanted to level out that
级别 如果我们想让它变得更平坦
horizon what we can do is just click on
地平线我们能做的就是点击
the rotate tool and then the left-click
旋转工具 然后左键单击
and a hold on this image and we could
抓住这张照片 我们就可以
try an eyeball it and get it to where we
试一试 然后把它带到我们需要的地方
want and then we can hit the rotate
想要 然后我们就可以轮换了
button or hit the enter key on the
按钮或按下
keyboard to actually rotate that and set
键盘来实际旋转并设置
those changes but if I do control Z
但如果我真的控制了Z
there's another way we can do this which
我们还有另一种方法可以做到这一点
is to create a guide we can hover over
就是创建一个我们可以悬停在上面的指南
it up here in this where it says how the
它就在这上面 上面写着
size of our image this kind of ruler
我们形象的大小这种尺子
area we can left-click and hold down the
我们可以左键单击并按住
left mouse button and then just move to
鼠标左键 然后移动到
the position we want and maybe we'll set
我们想要的位置 也许我们会设定
it right there and unclick now that
它就在那里 现在取消点击
creates this blue dotted line that we
创建这条蓝色虚线 我们
can use as a guide to rotate too we
也可以作为我们旋转的指南
could also do the same thing if we
也可以做同样的事情 如果我们
wanted to from the left we can drag
想从左边拖我们就可以了
another guide and we can drag as many as
另一个向导 我们可以拖动多个
we want we're gonna cover guides later
我们希望我们稍后会报道导游
but to get rid of guides we click on the
但是为了去掉指南 我们点击
move tool make sure we're we have
移动工具确保我们有
selected pick a layer or guide and you
选择拾取层或辅助线 然后您
can just drag it back off the screen and
只需将其拖回屏幕即可
it goes away so let's go back to the
它消失了 所以让我们回到
rotate tool and now if we left click and
旋转工具 现在如果我们左键单击并
hold we can rotate this and try to match
等等 我们可以旋转这个 然后试着匹配
it up with that line and that looks
它与那条线连在一起 看起来
pretty good there so we can hit the
那里很好 所以我们可以打到
enter key and now we've rotated this
Enter Key 现在我们已经旋转了这个
image and it looks much better although
形象 而且看起来好多了 尽管
we do have sort of a black area here
我们这里确实有一块黑色区域
this guide so see now we have some black
这本指南 现在我们有一些黑色的
corners where we rotated so we could
我们旋转的角落 所以我们可以
crop in we've learn how to do that using
我们已经学会了如何使用
the crop tool we can left-click and kind
我们可以左键单击并分类的裁剪工具
of create a crop area and sort of crop
创造一片庄稼区域和一种庄稼
this in nice how we want it to and then
这是我们想要的方式 然后
hit enter now we've got a nice cropped
现在按回车键 我们有一个很好的裁剪
image with a level horizon so that's one
具有水平地平线的图像 所以这是一个
method to do that I'll show you another
方法 我将向您展示另一个
method as well if you have an old image
如果您有一个旧图像 也可以使用
like this this is an Old World War two
像这样 这是一场旧的二战
image from somewhere in Europe but if we
来自欧洲某处的图像 但如果我们
go to if we grab the selection tool
如果我们抓住选择工具 请转到
added let's grab the crop tool actually
添加了让我们实际抓取裁剪工具
if we go to we want to crop this out but
如果我们去 我们想把这个剪掉 但是
we don't want to lose any of the other
我们不想失去任何其他人
pixels in the image well we would have
图像中的像素 我们将拥有
sort of a line we have a white line at
这条线上有一条白线
the top a white line at the bottom so if
顶部在底部有一条白线 因此如果
we wanted to rotate this before cropping
我们想在裁剪之前轮换一下
we could just do that with a guide we
我们可以在导游的带领下做到这点
could drag down a guide and then rotate
可以拖下一条辅助线然后旋转
to it and maybe I'll keep that guide
也许我会留着那本指南
there let me hit escape to get out of
在那里 我按下了逃生键才能离开
the crop tool one other thing we can do
裁剪工具还有一件事我们可以做
in the rotate though is we can
但在轮换中 我们可以
automatically crop as we rotate or as we
在我们旋转时或在我们
apply a rotate and to do that under the
应用旋转 并在
tools there's this clipping and right
工具有这样的剪裁和正确的
now it's set to adjust but if we click
现在它被设置为调整 但如果我们点击
on that we can go crop to result and so
在这一点上 我们可以进行裁剪和结果
if we set that to crop to result now
如果我们现在将其设置为裁剪结果
when we rotate this we can rotate it
当我们旋转这个的时候 我们可以旋转它
around to get it sort of where we want
把它弄到我们想要的地方
about level with that now we hit rotate
现在我们点击旋转 与之持平
and it automatically crops the image and
它会自动裁剪图像并
in this case it's it cropped it out with
在这种情况下 它是用它裁剪出来的
those white pixels around so I guess it
周围的白色像素 所以我猜
doesn't really help us much in this case
在这种情况下对我们帮助不大
but we can come back over and then grab
但我们可以回来 然后抓起
the crop tool and get pretty close to in
裁剪工具 并非常接近
there without losing a detail of the
在那里不会丢失任何细节
image and hit our Enter key now we've
图像并按回车键 现在我们已经
got a nice cropped image without losing
在没有丢失的情况下获得了一张很好的裁剪图像
those some of that corner cutting out
那些从角落里挖出来的东西
some of this corner detail and let's
一些角落的细节 让我们
talk to on the resize tool a little bit
在调整大小工具上稍作交流
or on to this scale tool so scale will
或者放到这个缩放工具上 这样缩放将
let us scale whatever is selected we
让我们扩展我们选择的任何内容
turned off that uniform scale so that's
关闭了制服刻度 所以
why it's allowing us to squish and sort
为什么它允许我们挤压和分类
of change this around again that's a
再次改变这一切 这是一个
keep aspect ratio as that box that'll
保持纵横比为框 这样可以
make it so we can scale uniformly also
这样我们也可以统一扩展
the Shift key if we hold down the shift
如果我们按住Shift键 按下Shift键
key on the keyboard it allows us to get
键盘上的按键它可以让我们得到
into that sort of mode where it's not
进入那种模式 在那里它不是
keeping the aspect
保持面貌
show it also behaves the same where it
显示它的行为也是相同的
has a preview if we don't have the
有一个预览 如果我们没有
preview selected it'll just show this
已选择预览 它将只显示以下内容
box and we can scale this box but we
盒子 我们可以缩放这个盒子 但我们
don't actually resize the image until we
不实际调整图像大小 直到我们
click scale and then it will just resize
点击比例 然后它就会调整大小
and again notice what it's doing if i
再次注意它在做什么 如果我
zoom out here notice what it's really
缩小到这里 注意它到底是什么
doing is scaling the image down and then
所做的就是缩小图像 然后
keeping the size of our original image
保持我们原始图像的大小
there I'll get rid of this guide again
在那里我会再次摆脱这位导游
and so we need to crop into this another
所以我们需要突然进入这个另一个
way to do resize if you just want to
如果您只是想要调整大小 这是一种方法
resize an image is that you can come up
调整图像的大小是因为您可以
here that's the one I use a lot I just
在这里 这是我经常使用的 我只是
go to image and then go to scale image
转到图像 然后转到缩放图像
and that gives us some more options for
这为我们提供了更多的选择
scaling it if you know a certain size
如果您知道某个大小 请按比例进行调整
you want it like 1920 wide listen would
你想要它就像1920年的Wide Listen
be like 1375 if we keep the aspect ratio
如果我们保持纵横比 就像1375
and you can even adjust the resolution
你甚至可以调整分辨率
to maybe something more like 96 dpi or
可能更像是96dpi或
you can have it be if you wanted to
如果你想的话 你可以拥有它
print it you can do 300 or 600 dpi we'll
打印它你可以做300或600 dpi 我们会
touch more on dpi in the future so don't
在未来更多地接触dpi 所以不要
worry that if that's throwing offer you
担心如果这是在抛出你的报价
don't understand it but here I'm
我不明白 但我在这里
basically upscaling this image I click
基本上放大我点击的这张图片
scale and it creates a larger image
缩放 它会创建更大的图像
without cutting off the sides I could
不需要切掉两边 我就可以
also go to image scale image and make it
也可以转到图像比例图像并制作它
incredibly tiny make it maybe 64 by 64
令人难以置信的微小 可能是64乘64
will distort it a little bit and hit
会把它稍微扭曲一下 然后
scale and then it shrinks it down but it
规模 然后缩小它 但它
doesn't get that transparency around the
不会让你的生活变得透明
outside of our image well hopefully you
在我们的形象之外 希望你
found that informative I want to show
发现我想要展示的信息量很大
you one more thing if we want to grab
你还有一件事如果我们想要抓住
this so we can go to select all I can do
这样我们就可以去选择我能做的一切
control C on my keyboard to copy the
按键盘上的C键复制
selected image and I could go paste this
选中的图像和我可以去粘贴这个
and I wanted to put it like a watermark
我想把它画成一个水印
on this image I can go ctrl V and it may
在这张图片上 我可以按Ctrl V 它可能
be larger than I want so what I can do
比我想要的要大 所以我能做的
is scale this down and looks like since
是缩小规模 看起来像是
this image is already grade scaled it's
这张图片已经过等级缩放了
going to put it's not going to show
我要说的是 它不会显示出来
color just the way that this image is so
颜色恰好就是这张图片的颜色
let's put on this one instead ctrl V we
让我们把这个换成ctrl V我们
have this nice image here or this nice
有这张很好的图像还是这张很好的
set yeah image that we pasted it on here
把我们贴在这里的图像设置好了
and we can use the scale tool to change
我们可以使用缩放工具来更改
the size of this
它的大小
I didn't turn that back on we can change
我没有打开它 我们可以改变
the size of this here and we can also
这里的大小 我们还可以
rotate it around as a separate layer
将其作为单独的层进行旋转
like we've learned in the in past videos
就像我们在过去的视频中学到的那样
hopefully that sheds some light on the
希望这能为我们提供一些线索
rotate and the scale tools go ahead and
旋转并继续缩放工具 然后
leave your questions and comments below
请在下面留下您的问题和评论
if you have any and I look forward to
如果你有的话 我很期待
catching you in the next video
在下一个视频中看到你